// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The prince abdicated the crown and returned to his castle. Abdicated means…",
    answer: "Gave up",
    options: [
      "Gave up",
      "Sold",
      "Reinvested into",
      "Auctioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The convicted criminal absconded prior to the sentencing phase of the trial. Absconded means…",
    answer: "Departed secretly",
    options: [
      "Touched the jury",
      "Reported immediately",
      "Left after discussion",
      "Departed secretly"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The aural component of balance is critical for postural control during ambulation. Aural means related to the…",
    answer: "Ear",
    options: [
      "Eye", 
      "Ear" ,
      "Nose",
      "Mouth"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The old man was benevolent with his fortune. Benevolent means…",
    answer: "Kind",
    options: [
      "Secretive",
      "Stingy",
      "Kind",
      "Careful"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The extra dirt was a key buttress to the foundation. Buttress means…",
    answer: "Support",
    options: [
      "Limiting factor",
      "Support",
      "Overwhelming condition",
      "Obstacle"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The cathode of a battery was removed. Cathode means…",
    answer: "Negative pole",
    options: [
      "Positive pole",
       "Negative pole",
       "Neutral pole",
       "Opposite pole"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The doctor was known as a charlatan over the years of his practice. Charlatan means…",
    answer: "Quack",
    options: [
      "Quack",
      "Knowledgeable physician",
      "Procedural physician",
      "Medical examiner"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The wound exhibited signs of copious drainage requiring medical intervention. Copious means…",
    answer: "Maximal",
    options: [
      "Minimal",
      "Clear" ,
      "Maximal",
      "Foul"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The attorney accused the witness of defaming the defendant. Defaming means…",
    answer: "Slandering",
    options: [
      "Killing",
      "Badgering",
      "Suffocating",
      "Slandering"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The detective was able to derive the facts of the case. Derive means…",
    answer: "Deduce",
    options: [
     "Desist",
     "Deter",
     "Devise",
     "Deduce"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Rohan is so magnanimous that everyone is always _____ to help him in his project.",
    answer: "eager",
    options: [
      "eager",
      "enthusiastic",
      "reluctant",
      "ignorant"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "I settled ______ Canada last year.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "at",
      "in",
      "off",
      "on"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Her ________ nature will help her realise the object of her desire.",
    answer: "obdurate",
    options: [
      "obdurate",
       "obstinate",
       "persevering",
       "fascinating"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 14,
    question: " I do not know what________ my father choose that particular school.",
    answer: "made",
    options: [
      "happened",
      "controlled",
      "made",
      "asked"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 15,
    question: " His arguments in the court were so ________ that he shattered the evidence built by the opposition lawyer.",
    answer: "penetrative",
    options: [
      "diagnostic",
      "voluminous",
      "penetrative",
      "worldly"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Since my father was an _____________ from India, he brought his Indian culture and traditions to the United States with him.",
    answer: "immigrant",
    options: [
      "emigrant",
      "immigrant",
      "native",
      "citizen"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "________ a country’s current account is in deficit, it would imply that its imports of goods and services are higher than its income from exports and remittances from non-residents.",
    answer: "If",
    options: [
      "As",
      "Given",
      "Unless",
      "If"
    ]
  } ,
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "It is time you ________ home",
    answer: "went",
    options: [
       "go",
       "went",
       "come",
       "reach"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "None of the food was wasted _______",
    answer: "was it",
    options: [
      "wasn't",
      "was it",
      "weren’t",
      "were it",
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 20,
    question: " He found the jewellery box empty. All the ornaments, jewels, etc were ________",
    answer: "stolen",
    options: [
      "protected",
     "seized",
      "sold",
      "stolen"
    ]
  }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];